Haroldo dos Reis Carvalho

LinkedIn | GitHub

+55 (11) 9 3437-5071

<u>carvalhoh@gmail.com</u>

<u>pydevhc@gmail.com</u>

Rua Vilfredo Pareto, 84 Chácara da Enseada CEP:

04963-115

São Paulo/SP - Brasil

OBJECTIVE MACHINE LEARNING - AI

RESUME

Python Developer in Machine Learning – AI in training at Udemy - EAD and Technology platform, Digital Games Technologist student at Estácio de Sá University (UNESA). Professional with a resilient, proactive, and communicative profile. Currently, I am taking some courses to gain more knowledge in some areas and programming languages. I'm transitioning areas and I don't have active experience in the programming area, but I gain a lot of knowledge in the main technologies:

- Proficient in Python | Data Science
- Front-End skills | HTML | CSS | JavaScript | React.js | SASS | Database | Game Design |
- Object Oriented Programming
- Knowledge with Git/GitHub
- · Ability to build interfaces that consume APIs.

EDUCATION

- Digital Games Technologist Estácio de Sá University (UNESA) January/2023 to December/2024
- Full Stack Web Developer Udemy EAD and Technology platform completed in 2023
- Python Developer Udemy EAD and Technology platform completed in 2023
- Al Developer Machine Learning Data Science Udemy EAD and Technology platform

EXPERIENCE

Haganá (São Paulo/SP)

07/2021 - Atual

(Empresa de Segurança Grande Porte)

SSO - Safety Security Officer

- Safety Security Officer LinkedIn Global Security is a trusted advisor and leader in supporting an educated, engaged workforce that practices sound security principles, keeping LinkedIn safe and secure. Responsible for overseeing LinkedIn floors and all personnel located in the central office. Supervise alarm monitoring activities, applying the property security procedure to maintain established security and normality meeting customer demands, IDF/MDF rooms, and all facilities in conjunction with the GSOC main Security headquarters in California. Meetings with the local facilities manager and coordinator. Make sure the site is always secure.
- Quality customer service to clients from different countries, providing unique experience within the office.
- Participation in the implementation of a new management method for the Transfer service provided to employees coming from other offices outside Brazil.
- Contribution to the improvement of internal office processes, especially in the organization of daily activities through the creation of spreadsheets and workflow diagrams.
- Member of the fire brigade team, providing First Aid in cases of emergencies or accidents.

GRUPO GPS 07/2018 – 06/2021

(Empresa de Segurança Grande Porte)

VSP - Body Guard VIP - 12/2020 - 06/2021

 Responsible for supervising and ensuring the security of the VIP and their property, using the progressive use of force if necessary stipulated in ordinance 3,233/82. Meet customer demands, supervise compliance with customer rules and resolutions.

Operational Supervisor - 11/2019 - 12/2020

Responsible for supervising security and contracts and maintaining routine monitoring, applying the property
security procedure, visiting service stations, meeting customer demands, monitoring compliance with
customer standards and resolutions, preparing work schedules, checking employees and relocating security
guards to compensate for absences, check the personal presentation of employees, supervise the execution
of electronic patrols, point out places of high risk, inspect safety equipment, check the condition of vehicles,
monitor the preparation of police reports, maintain CNV and up-to-date recycling, overseeing the entire
security area, assisting the coordinator in his tasks, meeting demands, preparing reports, delegating tasks
and passing on guidance.

Electronic Operational Supervisor – 07/2018 – 11/2019

 Responsible for supervising security and contracts and maintaining monitoring routine, applying the access control security procedures, visiting service contracts, meeting customer demands, monitoring compliance with customer standards.

CSO GLOBAL 08/2017 - 03/2018

Operational Manager

- Managed a variety of clients and general administration of the business.
- Technical responsible for electronics, focusing on maintaining access control.

AIG Seguros 01/2016 - 11/2016

Operational Supervisor

Managed 2 sales cells and general administration of the Auto and non-Auto sales business.

Netflix 04/2015 - 01/2016

Bilingual Operational Supervisor

Supervised a technical support and customer chat support team.

<u>Teleperformance</u> 03/2012 - 10/2014

Operational coordinator

 Coordinated 3 customer support operations. The operations under my responsibility were: Amway, Hotel.com and Nokia/Windows.

<u>US NAVY</u> 04/1998 - 04/2003

DC2 Petty Officer

• US Navy Petty Officer aboard the frigate USS Underwood 36. Participated in special tactical missions against terrorism and patrolling the east coast of the United States.

LANGUAGES

Fluent English
 Spanish intermediary
 Native Portuguese

SKILLS

HTML
 Python
 React.js
 Numpy
 Git/GitHub

CSS
 SASS
 Matplotlib
 API Rest
 Pandas

JavascriptScikit-Learn